&gt;&gt; Self-driving car engineers today use
— 如今 无人驾驶汽车工程师使用
two distinct approaches to autonomous development,
两种不同的途径进行无人驾驶技术的研发
a robotics approach, and a deep learning approach.
一种是利用机器人技术 另一种则是利用深度学习技术
The robotics approach fuses output from a suite of sensors
机器人技术通过融合一套传感器的输出数据
to directly measure the vehicle surroundings and then navigate accordingly.
来直接测量车辆周边环境 然后以此进行导航
Self-driving car engineers have been working on
在过去很多年里 无人驾驶车工程师团队一直在
and perfecting the robotics approach for many years.
努力完善机器人技术
&gt;&gt; More recently, engineering teams have begun to use
— 近年来 工程团队开始以深度学习技术
deep learning as a different approach for developing autonomous vehicles.
作为研发无人驾驶汽车的途径
Deep neural networks allow self-driving cars to learn how to drive,
深度神经网络可以让无人驾驶汽车
by mimicking human driving behavior.
通过模仿人类驾驶行为来学习如何驾驶
Both, the robotics and deep learning methods,
这两种途径 利用机器人技术和深度学习技术
are actively being pursued today in the development of self-driving cars.
现在都普遍应用到了无人驾驶汽车开发过程中
&gt;&gt; So in this Nanodegree program,
— 因此 在这一纳米学位课程中
you'll be working with both approaches.
你将会同时用到这两种方法
That way, you, as an engineer,
这样 你作为工程师
will be prepared to work anywhere.
就能做好充分准备胜任相关工作
By the end of this program you'll be teaming up with other students to actually write
本次课程结束后 你将和其他学生组队 亲自编写机器人代码和深度学习代码
both robotics and deep learning code to control a real self-driving car. Pretty Cool.
去控制一辆真正的无人驾驶汽车 这非常酷
&gt;&gt; Along the way you'll work through several modules,
— 在此期间 你需要学习几个模块
with each one focusing on a different layer of the self-driving car technology stack,
每个模块讲解无人驾驶技术中的一层
and after each module,
学习完每个模块后
you'll build a project to demonstrate what you've learned,
你需要完成一个项目 以展现你所掌握的知识
and you'll get real human feedback on your work.
我们有专人对你的项目提供反馈意见
This first module that you're going through now is
现在 你需要学习的第一个模块内容不多
smaller and should only take a week or so to complete.
仅需一周左右即可完成
Later modules will be longer and may take up to a month.
后面的模块内容较多 可能需要长达一个月的时间来完成
&gt;&gt; In addition to receiving human feedback on your projects,
— 除了能收到关于项目的专业审阅反馈
you'll also have access to the forums where you
你还可以访问论坛
can ask questions and get to know your fellow students.
提出问题 并和你的同学交流互动
And of course our team is here to help you succeed.
当然 我们的团队会一直提供支持 帮助你完成本项目
So be sure to reach out and keep in touch.
请与我们保持联络 如需帮助 请随时联系我们